<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quick on Tender Meat Love</title>
    <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/tags/quick/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quick on Tender Meat Love</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright 2008-2018 Josh Rendek</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 01:18:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tendermeatlove.com/tags/quick/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Charred carrots</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/08/charred-carrots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/08/charred-carrots/</guid>
      <description> Preheat oven to 425 degrees (convection roast) Peel carrots, cut in half, then cut in half length-wise Toss in olive oil, thyme, salt, and pepper Pre-heat pan in oven for 5 minutes Cook in oven for 10 minutes Flip carrots Cook another 8-10 minutes Drizzle with a very small amount of honey and chipotle pepper, toss to coat and serve  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pan seared marinated skirt steak</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/pan-seared-marinated-skirt-steak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/pan-seared-marinated-skirt-steak/</guid>
      <description> Marinate the steak for about an hour in the ingredients above Preheat oven to 170 Heat non-stick pan over high heat (7-8) Put steak into pan and sear each side 1.5 minutes Pour extra sauce + a little water into sauce pot and boil for 30 seconds Put steak into oven and let it rest and come to temp for 10 minutes Slice and serve, top with sauce  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosemary and Oregano chicken breasts</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/rosemary-and-oregano-chicken-breasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/rosemary-and-oregano-chicken-breasts/</guid>
      <description> Heat non-stick pan over medium-high heat (6.5) Butterfly chicken breasts and pat both sides dry Rub with salt, pepper, oregano and rosemary Add oil to pan Cook chicken with lid on for ~4 minutes each side  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sauted Apples</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/sauted-apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/sauted-apples/</guid>
      <description> Heat non-stick pan over medium-high heat Use an apple slicer to cut your apple and core it into wedges (peel skin if you don&amp;rsquo;t want it) Add butter to pan and add apples Add water and sprinkle with sugar and cinnamon Cook 5-10 minutes until apples are soft and browned  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baguette w/ Mozzarella, Tomato, Basil</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/baguette-w/-mozzarella-tomato-basil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/baguette-w/-mozzarella-tomato-basil/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat broiler Slice baguette into 1&amp;frasl;2 inch slices and coat each side with a small amount of olive oil Add a basil leaf, tomato, and then a slice of mozzarella to each Season with salt, pepper, and dried oregano and rosemary Broil for ~5-8 minutes, wait for it to melt / get brown and crispy Serve and drizzle with extra virgin olive oil to finish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick White Pizza</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/quick-white-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/quick-white-pizza/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat oven to 450 F (check pre-made crust instructions). Brush bottom of crust with butter. Brush top of crust with olive oil. Add mozarella to cover and shred a small amount of gruyere. Slice chorizo into small slices and add to pizza with vegetables. Bake for 10 minutes (follow pre-made instructions).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic mashed fingerling potatoes</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/garlic-mashed-fingerling-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/garlic-mashed-fingerling-potatoes/</guid>
      <description> Wash potatoes and smash the garlic Put them into a sauce pot with enough water to cover Bring to a boil, then cook covered for ~15 minutes until tender Mash and add buttermilk, and season to taste with salt and pepper  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacque&#39;s Pear/Apple Tart</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/jacques-pear/apple-tart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/jacques-pear/apple-tart/</guid>
      <description> Line pan with foil/silicon sheet Preheat oven to 400 F and put pan in oven with butter to melt (~1 minute) Take pan out, rub both sides of tortilla into the butter, put sugar on one side and flip it over (sugar side down). Put sliced pear/apple/fruit on tortilla and add little dots of butter around the fruit Sprinkle with sugar Bake 10 minutes Heat up apricot preserves for 30 seconds in microwave Take tortilla out of oven, cut into 4 pieces and brush with a small amount of preserves  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacque&#39;s Stovetop Flat Bread</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/jacques-stovetop-flat-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/jacques-stovetop-flat-bread/</guid>
      <description> Mix everything except the 2 tbsp of water together Heat non-stick skillet over medium/medium-high heat Add 1 tbsp olive oil and pour dough into pan and spread it out flat Add 1-2 tbsp water on the edges and cover with lid. Cook 8-10 minutes (check and make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t burn the bottom) Flip, recover, cook for 5 minutes to finish. Serve warm  Variations:
 Caramelize onions. Pour batter in, then add onions on top of dough once you pour it in, then flip it like normal  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>