<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bread on Tender Meat Love</title>
    <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/tags/bread/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bread on Tender Meat Love</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright 2008-2018 Josh Rendek</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tendermeatlove.com/tags/bread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Bread</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/banana-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/banana-bread/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat oven to 350 and butter a bread pan Mash the bananas until smooth and stir in melted butter Mix in baking soda, salt, sugar, egg, and vanilla extract Mix in flour Pour batter into pan Bake for 50 minutes to 1 hour Let cool for 20 minutes then remove from pan, and let completely cool  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zucchini Bread</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/zucchini-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/zucchini-bread/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat oven to 325 Grease and flour two bread pans Mix flour, salt, baking powder, baking soda, and cinnamon together in bowl Beat eggs, oil, vanilla, and sugar together in another bowl Add dry ingredients to wet and mix Add zucchini and nuts and mix Pour batter into pans Bake for 40-60 minutes Let cool for 20 minutes, then remove from pan and cool completely Try and get ~10 slices per loaf  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacque&#39;s Stovetop Flat Bread</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/jacques-stovetop-flat-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/jacques-stovetop-flat-bread/</guid>
      <description> Mix everything except the 2 tbsp of water together Heat non-stick skillet over medium/medium-high heat Add 1 tbsp olive oil and pour dough into pan and spread it out flat Add 1-2 tbsp water on the edges and cover with lid. Cook 8-10 minutes (check and make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t burn the bottom) Flip, recover, cook for 5 minutes to finish. Serve warm  Variations:
 Caramelize onions. Pour batter in, then add onions on top of dough once you pour it in, then flip it like normal  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>