<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Main dish on Tender Meat Love</title>
    <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/categories/main-dish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Main dish on Tender Meat Love</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright 2008-2018 Josh Rendek</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tendermeatlove.com/categories/main-dish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BBQ Brisket</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/bbq-brisket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/bbq-brisket/</guid>
      <description>Trim brisket(s) of fat cap and silver skin Pour 2 tbsp liquid smoke over brisket and rub with onion salt and garlic salt Wrap brisket in foil tightly and refrigerate over night Preheat oven to 300F Unwrap brisket and place in roasting pan, cover tightly with foil and bake for 5-6 hours Let rest for 30-45 minutes and then slice To make BBQ sauce: in a sauce pan mix brown sugar, ketchup, butter, water, celery salt, 1 tbsp liquid smoke, Worcesteshire sauce, mustard powder, Dr Pepper/Coke, and salt and pepper until boiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sous Vide Rump Roast</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/sous-vide-rump-roast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/sous-vide-rump-roast/</guid>
      <description> Pat the rump roast dry with paper towels Form a crust on the roast with salt, pepper, and sugar Setup a sous vide bag for your roast and add the butter Turn the sous vide on 138F and cook for 18-36 hours (20h last time) Once finished sear roast on all sides in a hot skillet Save drippings from bag and make a pan gravy with milk if you have any, reduce until thick  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Filet w/ Mushroom Sauce</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/pork-filet-w/-mushroom-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/12/pork-filet-w/-mushroom-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Cut the pork into 1-2 inch thick medallions, and then flatten to make a consistent size Chop rosemary finely, mix with salt and pepper on a plate, and then roll all the pork medallions in the mixture Use another plate and put the rice flour in it. Roll the medallions to cover them in the rice flour Slice the mushrooms and heat a stainless steel pan over medium-high heat. Cook 4-5 minutes or until browned Set mushrooms aside in a bowl Add a tbsp of oil and tbsp of butter to the pan if needed Cook medallions until brown on each side, then roll the sides to let the oil hit them Cook in batches and then set medallions aside On medium high heat, add the white wine and deglaze the pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked Chicken Wings</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/09/smoked-chicken-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/09/smoked-chicken-wings/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat smoker to 275 for 45 minutes before hand Lower to 225-250 when cooking Combine spices and rub all over chicken Let wings rest for an hour Add chips/wood to smoker Smoke for 2-2.5 hours, internal temp should be 160F Prep charcoal grill Finish/crisp wings up on grill for 2-5 minutes and serve  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked Duck Breast</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/09/smoked-duck-breast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/09/smoked-duck-breast/</guid>
      <description> Mix juice, salt, sugar, spices and put duck in to brine. Let marinate for 4 hours. Pre-heat smoker to 275 for 45 minutes before hand Lower to 250 when cooking Smoke for 2-3 hours, internal temp should be 150F Prep charcoal grill Finish/crisp up on grill for 2-5 minutes and serve  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked Sausage</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/09/smoked-sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/09/smoked-sausage/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat smoker to 275 for 45 minutes before hand Lower to 225-250 when cooking Smoke for 2-3 hours, internal temp should be 160F Prep charcoal grill Finish/crisp up on grill for 2-5 minutes and serve  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pan seared marinated skirt steak</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/pan-seared-marinated-skirt-steak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/pan-seared-marinated-skirt-steak/</guid>
      <description> Marinate the steak for about an hour in the ingredients above Preheat oven to 170 Heat non-stick pan over high heat (7-8) Put steak into pan and sear each side 1.5 minutes Pour extra sauce + a little water into sauce pot and boil for 30 seconds Put steak into oven and let it rest and come to temp for 10 minutes Slice and serve, top with sauce  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosemary and Oregano chicken breasts</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/rosemary-and-oregano-chicken-breasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 01:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/rosemary-and-oregano-chicken-breasts/</guid>
      <description> Heat non-stick pan over medium-high heat (6.5) Butterfly chicken breasts and pat both sides dry Rub with salt, pepper, oregano and rosemary Add oil to pan Cook chicken with lid on for ~4 minutes each side  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinach stuffed pork chop</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/spinach-stuffed-pork-chop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 00:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/spinach-stuffed-pork-chop/</guid>
      <description> Dice and add the tomatoes, chicken broth and white wine in a bowl for later Heat in a skillet over high heat Add spinach, nutmeg, garlic, salt and pepper. Cook for 3 minutes Transfer to a plate and cool, mix in gruyere Butterfly pork chops and season the outsides w/ salt and pepper Saute over high heat for 3.5 minutes on each side (make sure center is cooked / to temp) Put on a dish to rest Add scallions and garlic to pan drippings and saute for 30 seconds Add white wine, tomatoes, and chicken broth to pan Boil for 2 minutes to reduce Stir in the olives and mix well Coat the pork chops and garnish with cilantro  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bean Salad</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/bean-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/bean-salad/</guid>
      <description> Cook and cool rice Drain and rinse black beans Slice celery into small pieces Mince garlic Thaw/cook corn partially Dice bell pepper and jalapeno Mix everything together in bowl Add 1&amp;frasl;2 bottle of Italian dressing and season with salt and pepper to taste  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick White Pizza</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/quick-white-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/quick-white-pizza/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat oven to 450 F (check pre-made crust instructions). Brush bottom of crust with butter. Brush top of crust with olive oil. Add mozarella to cover and shred a small amount of gruyere. Slice chorizo into small slices and add to pizza with vegetables. Bake for 10 minutes (follow pre-made instructions).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broiled Tilapia w/ Mustard Chive Sauce</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/broiled-tilapia-w/-mustard-chive-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/broiled-tilapia-w/-mustard-chive-sauce/</guid>
      <description> Pre-heat broiler and line a cooking tray with foil Pat fish dry and then brush fish with S&amp;amp;P and olive oil Cook 4-8 minutes (depends on stove) Mix everything else together for the sauce, drizzle over fish before serving  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Chops w/ Apples and Garlic Mash</title>
      <link>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/pork-chops-w/-apples-and-garlic-mash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 20:18:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tendermeatlove.com/2018/07/pork-chops-w/-apples-and-garlic-mash/</guid>
      <description> Put potatoes and garlic in a sauce pan, cover with water and bring to boil. Uncover, cook for 15 minutes Rub pork chop with sage, salt and pepper Heat skillet or non-stick pan over medium high heat and add 1 tbsp oil Sear both sides for ~5 minutes (depends on thickness and stove) and set aside Add apples and red onion wedges and cook until brown, ~5 minutes Add S&amp;amp;P and mix in cider Add pork chops and cook ~5 minutes Drain potatoes, reserve 1&amp;frasl;4 cup liquid Add buttermilk to potatoes, mash, add salt and pepper to taste Drizzle the potatoes and pork chops with pan juices and serve  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>